(Raj:)Really? Then what were you doing
at the comic book store that night?
(Girl:)I've been trying to force myself
into situations I'm not comfortable with.
(Girl:)I saw the flyer in the store window
and I made myself go in.
(Girl:)I don't even like comic books.
- Yeah, me neither.
- What were you doing there?
(Raj:)I lied. I love them.
(Raj:)I only said that so you'd go out with me.
(Girl:)You don't want to do that.
(Girl:)I'm kind of broken.
(Raj:)That's great. I'm broken too.
(Girl:)- No, you're not.
- I totally am.
(Raj:)If it wasn't for this beer, I couldn't even
talk to you right now. I'm a wreck.
(Raj:)There are many things
seriously wrong with me.
(Raj:)And not quirks either...
(Raj:)...like, diagnosable psychological problems.
(Raj:)Maybe brain damage.
(Girl:)Well, how do I know
you're not just saying that?